<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="privacy_article_body"><![CDATA[Anky, Inc. - Effective June 7, 2026

The short version: Anky is local-first. Your writing stays on your device unless you choose to export it, back it up, contact support, or ask Anky for a reflection. When you ask for a reflection, your writing is sent to Anky’s mirror service and AI providers so a reflection can be generated. We use providers that do not store your writing. We do not sell your data, use it for advertising, or use your writing to train our own models.

## 1. Who We Are

Anky is operated by **Anky, Inc.**, a Delaware corporation.

Contact: **[support@anky.app](mailto:support@anky.app)**

## 2. What Anky Is

Anky is a local-first writing and reflection app. The core artifact is the `.anky` file: a forward-only writing session created under constraint. The app lets you write, save, revisit, export, import, delete, and optionally reflect on that writing.

Anky is not a therapist, medical service, crisis service, financial advisor, legal advisor, or spiritual authority.

## 3. What Stays On Your Device By Default

The following data is stored locally on your device unless you choose to export it, back it up, recover it elsewhere, contact support, or request a reflection:

- Your `.anky` writing files
- Active writing drafts
- Reconstructed readable writing
- Local reflections returned by Anky
- Session history and Map data
- Local app settings and daily reminder settings
- Local Anky access information and private recovery material
- Local credit balance cache
- Local export/import files you create

Writing, saving, revealing, copying, browsing Map, and viewing local history do not require sending your writing to Anky’s server.

## 4. What Leaves Your Device

Data leaves your device when you ask Anky for a reflection or writing nudge, buy or restore credits, enable backup/export/import features, contact support, or use device trial and safety checks.

When you tap **Ask Anky** or request a writing nudge, the app sends the exact `.anky` file bytes to Anky’s mirror service. The mirror verifies the request, verifies the `.anky` format and hash, reconstructs readable text, sends the writing and prompt to AI service providers, receives the generated reflection or nudge, returns it to your device, and checks/spends one reflection credit after a successful reflection.

The returned reflection is stored locally on your device.

Purchases are processed by Google Play and managed through RevenueCat. We do not receive or store your credit card number. Credit operations use purchase records, credit balances, product identifiers, entitlement information, app user identifiers, transaction status, and related metadata to grant and manage reflection credits.

Anky creates a private local profile for your device. Reflection and nudge requests include limited verification metadata so the mirror service can accept the request, prevent abuse, and return credits to the right profile. Your private recovery material is not sent to Anky.

For free trials, fraud prevention, abuse prevention, and request safety, the app may ask Android platform integrity or device attestation services for a token when supported. Reflection and nudge requests may send that token to the mirror service as trial proof.

When you enable backup, recovery, export, import, sharing, or support features, selected writing, reflections, recovery information, or related files may be stored by Android device storage, Android backup services, the destination you choose, or the email/support provider you contact.

## 5. What We Do Not Collect

Anky does not require:

- Your legal name
- Your phone number
- Your contacts
- Your precise location
- Your camera, microphone, or photos
- Your social accounts
- A traditional username/password login

Anky does not sell personal data, use your writing for advertising, or use your writing to train Anky-owned AI models.

## 6. Third-Party Services

Anky uses third-party services for app features:

- **Google** - Google Play purchases, refunds, device services, Android backup services when enabled, notifications, device attestation, and platform services.
- **RevenueCat** - purchase management, credit balances, entitlements, and transaction records.
- **OpenRouter** and **AI model providers** - routing and generating reflections from text you choose to send.
- **Cloud hosting / infrastructure providers** - operating Anky’s mirror service, logs, security, and reliability.
- **Email/support providers** - receiving and responding to support requests.

These providers process data according to their own terms and privacy policies.

## 7. AI Processing

When you ask for a reflection, your writing is processed by AI systems. AI-generated reflections can be inaccurate, incomplete, unexpected, emotionally intense, or not useful. They are generated automatically and should not be treated as professional advice.

We design Anky’s mirror service to avoid permanently storing raw `.anky` writing, reconstructed writing, or reflection text unless needed for a user-requested support/debugging flow, security, abuse prevention, legal compliance, or another clearly stated purpose.

## 8. Operational Metadata

To operate Anky, we collect and process limited metadata such as Anky support ID or app user identifier, request timestamps and hashes, app version, platform, credit balance and transaction records, purchase product identifiers, error states, provider usage metadata, security signals, and support request metadata.

We use this data to provide reflections, manage credits, prevent abuse, debug issues, respond to support, comply with law, and operate the service.

## 9. Payments

Payments are handled by Google Play and managed with RevenueCat. We do not receive your full payment card details. Refunds, billing disputes, and purchase history are handled according to Google Play policies.

## 10. Tokens And Public References

Anky may display token or public-reference information when those features are available. Your private recovery material remains on your device unless you export, reveal, back up, or otherwise share it. Never share your recovery words. Some token, transaction, and public-reference information can be public by nature. Anky cannot delete information written to public networks.

## 11. Data Retention

Local data remains on your device until you delete it, delete the app, reset the app, or remove backups. Reflection-related metadata, purchase records, and support emails are retained as long as needed to operate the service, manage credits, prevent fraud or abuse, comply with legal obligations, resolve disputes, maintain security, and respond to you.

## 12. Deletion

You can delete local writing, local reflections, private access, and local app data from inside the app where deletion tools are available, or by deleting the app from your device. Deleting the app does not delete exported/shared files, Android or device backups, Google Play records, RevenueCat records, support emails, backend metadata needed for security/credit/legal reasons, or public network data.

To request deletion of data Anky controls, contact **[support@anky.app](mailto:support@anky.app)**.

## 13. Children

Anky is not intended for children under 13. If you are under 18, use Anky only with permission from a parent or guardian. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13.

## 14. Your Rights

Depending on where you live, your rights can include access, correction, deletion, export, restriction, or objection to certain uses of your personal data. Because Anky is local-first, much of your data is only on your device and can be managed by you directly. For requests about data Anky controls, contact **[support@anky.app](mailto:support@anky.app)**.

## 15. Security

We use reasonable technical and organizational measures to protect data we process. No system is perfectly secure. You are responsible for protecting your device, passcode, recovery words, exported files, Android account, and any place where you store or share your writing.

## 16. International Users

Anky, Inc. is based in the United States. Data sent to Anky or its service providers is processed in the United States or other countries where those providers operate.

## 17. Changes

We update this Privacy Policy when the policy changes. Continued use of Anky after changes means you accept the updated policy.

## 18. Contact

**Anky, Inc.**

Contact: **[support@anky.app](mailto:support@anky.app)**]]></string>

    <string name="terms_article_body"><![CDATA[Anky, Inc. - Effective June 7, 2026

Important: Anky is a writing and reflection app. It is not therapy, medical care, crisis support, financial advice, legal advice, or spiritual authority. By using Anky, you agree that you remain responsible for your writing, your decisions, your device, your recovery words, your purchases, and how you use AI-generated reflections.

## 1. Acceptance

These Terms and Conditions are an agreement between you and **Anky, Inc.**, a Delaware corporation. By downloading, accessing, or using Anky, you agree to these Terms. If you do not agree, do not use Anky.

## 2. What Anky Provides

Anky lets you write forward-only `.anky` sessions, save writing locally, revisit local writing history, export or import writing files, manage private Anky access, buy or use reflection credits, ask Anky for AI-generated reflections, and use related features we provide over time. We may change, suspend, or discontinue any part of Anky at any time.

## 3. Age Requirement

Anky is not intended for children under 13. If you are under 18, you may use Anky only with permission from a parent or guardian. By using Anky, you represent that you meet these requirements.

## 4. Anky Is Not Professional Advice

Anky is not a therapist, doctor, emergency service, financial advisor, legal advisor, religious authority, or spiritual authority. AI-generated reflections are for personal writing reflection only. They may be inaccurate, incomplete, unexpected, emotionally intense, or not useful. Do not rely on Anky for medical, mental health, legal, financial, emergency, or safety decisions. If you may hurt yourself or someone else, or if you are in immediate danger, contact local emergency services or a trusted person immediately.

## 5. Your Writing

You own your writing. By using Anky, you give Anky, Inc. limited permission to process your writing only as needed to provide the features you choose, such as saving locally, generating a reflection, exporting, importing, backing up, debugging, support, security, and abuse prevention. You are responsible for what you write, export, send, share, or back up. Do not use Anky in a way that violates the law or harms others.

## 6. Local-First Design

Anky is designed to be local-first. Your writing normally stays on your device. When you ask for a reflection, you understand that your writing is sent to Anky’s mirror service and AI service providers to generate the reflection. We use providers that do not store your writing. When you export, share, back up, or contact support, you are choosing to send or store data outside the app.

## 7. Private Access And Recovery

Anky may create private local access for your device. You are responsible for protecting your recovery words, device passcode, biometric access, account backups, and exported files. Never share your recovery words. If you lose them, Anky may not be able to restore your credits, profile state, or related data.

## 8. Purchases, Credits, and Refunds

Writing in Anky is free. Reflections may require credits. Credits are digital app credits used only inside Anky for reflection requests. Credits are not money, not cryptocurrency, not stored value, not withdrawable, not redeemable for cash, and not transferable unless we explicitly say otherwise. Purchases are processed through Google Play and may be managed by RevenueCat. Refunds are handled by Google Play.

## 9. AI-Generated Reflections

AI-generated reflections are produced automatically. They may be wrong, miss context, sound too certain, be emotionally uncomfortable, misunderstand language or intent, contain unexpected content, or be unavailable because of technical errors. You remain responsible for interpreting and using any reflection.

## 10. Token References

Anky may display token references, public references, or related information. These references are informational only. Nothing in Anky is financial advice, investment advice, tax advice, legal advice, or an offer to buy or sell any token, security, or asset. Using Anky does not require buying, holding, or trading any token.

## 11. User Conduct

You agree not to use Anky if you do not meet the age requirements; use Anky for illegal activity; abuse, attack, disrupt, or overload Anky’s systems; circumvent credits, paywalls, trials, attestation, or security controls; reverse engineer or publish private prompts or backend systems; use automation to abuse the app; access another person’s data or recovery words; violate another person’s rights; generate instructions for harming yourself or others; or misrepresent Anky.

We may suspend, restrict, or terminate access if we believe you violated these Terms, abused the service, created risk, or used Anky unlawfully.

## 12. Intellectual Property

Anky, Inc. owns Anky’s software, design, name, logos, characters, visual assets, prompts, product concepts, documentation, and related intellectual property. You may not copy, modify, distribute, sell, reverse engineer, or create derivative works from Anky except where allowed by law or by an open-source license we explicitly provide. You retain ownership of your own writing.

## 13. Feedback

If you send us feedback, ideas, suggestions, bug reports, or feature requests, you give Anky, Inc. permission to use them without restriction or compensation. This does not give us ownership of your private writing.

## 14. Third-Party Services

Anky depends on third-party services, which may include Google, RevenueCat, OpenRouter, AI model providers, cloud hosting providers, email providers, and public networks. We are not responsible for third-party services, terms, outages, policies, prices, decisions, or data practices.

## 15. App Store Terms

If you downloaded Anky from Google Play, Google’s terms also apply. Google is not responsible for Anky, its content, support, warranties, or claims, except as required by applicable law or Google’s own terms.

## 16. Availability

Anky may be unavailable, delayed, interrupted, inaccurate, or discontinued. We do not guarantee that Anky will always work, that reflections will always be available, that credits will always sync instantly, or that local data will never be lost. Back up anything important.

## 17. Termination

You may stop using Anky at any time. You can delete the app and delete local data where the app provides deletion tools. We may suspend, limit, or terminate your access if necessary to protect Anky, users, third parties, or the integrity of the service.

## 18. Disclaimer of Warranties

ANKY IS PROVIDED "AS IS" AND "AS AVAILABLE." TO THE FULLEST EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW, ANKY, INC. DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED. YOUR USE OF ANKY IS AT YOUR OWN RISK.

## 19. Limitation of Liability

TO THE FULLEST EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW, ANKY, INC. AND ITS OWNERS, DIRECTORS, OFFICERS, EMPLOYEES, CONTRACTORS, SERVICE PROVIDERS, AND AFFILIATES WILL NOT BE LIABLE FOR INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, CONSEQUENTIAL, EXEMPLARY, OR PUNITIVE DAMAGES, LOST PROFITS, LOST DATA, LOST WRITING, LOST CREDITS, LOST TOKENS, LOST RECOVERY ACCESS, DEVICE COMPROMISE, EMOTIONAL DISTRESS, OR DECISIONS MADE BASED ON AI-GENERATED CONTENT. ANKY, INC.’S TOTAL LIABILITY FOR ANY CLAIM WILL NOT EXCEED THE GREATER OF THE AMOUNT YOU PAID THROUGH THE APP IN THE 12 MONTHS BEFORE THE CLAIM OR $50 USD. Some jurisdictions do not allow certain limitations.

## 20. Indemnification

You agree to defend, indemnify, and hold harmless Anky, Inc. and its owners, directors, officers, employees, contractors, service providers, and affiliates from claims, damages, losses, liabilities, costs, and expenses arising from your use of Anky, your writing or exported content, your violation of these Terms, your violation of law, your violation of another person’s rights, your misuse of AI-generated reflections, or your token, transaction, or recovery activity.

## 21. Governing Law

These Terms are governed by the laws of the State of Delaware, without regard to conflict-of-law principles, except where your local law requires otherwise.

## 22. Disputes and Arbitration

To the fullest extent permitted by law, disputes between you and Anky, Inc. will be resolved through binding individual arbitration, not in a class action or jury trial. You and Anky, Inc. agree to bring claims only on an individual basis. This section does not prevent either party from seeking relief in small claims court or seeking injunctive relief for intellectual property, security, or unauthorized access issues. If this section is not enforceable where you live, the rest of these Terms still apply.

## 23. Changes

We may update these Terms from time to time. Continued use of Anky after changes means you accept the updated Terms.

## 24. Contact

**Anky, Inc.**

Contact: **[support@anky.app](mailto:support@anky.app)**]]></string>

    <string name="token_article_body"><![CDATA[$ANKY lives on Base. The app can open a Stripe-hosted crypto onramp into your local Anky wallet, but Anky does not provide financial advice, price promises, custody, or in-app selling.

## what it points to

anky is a writing practice. you sit down, you write for 8 minutes without stopping, and something emerges that your conscious mind did not plan. the token does not change what the practice is. it does not unlock features, grant app access, or replace credits. it is only the memetic layer around the practice.

## before you buy

Stripe may only offer supported crypto assets and networks in your region. If $ANKY is not available directly in Stripe, the onramp funds your Anky wallet on Base instead of completing a $ANKY swap. Selling or moving funds requires exporting your wallet and using a compatible external service.

the mirror does not care about the price. the practice remains free. write for 8 minutes. meet yourself. the words you wrote are still yours.]]></string>
</resources>
